(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T22:15:28.419232",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
いっせーので鳴り響いたスタートの合図
The starting signal echoed with a "Ready, set, go!"
なぞった線で結んだ世界 色付いていく
The world connected by traced lines fills with color,
ここから
starting right here!
かくれんぼ
[Hide-and-Seek]
物心がついた頃 既にここにあった
By the time I came to my senses, it was already here...
僕じゃない誰かの記憶は
Memories of someone who isn't me
夕日とともに蘇る
revive along with the setting sun.
古ぼけた絵本を取り出して
Taking out a worn-out picture book,
落書きの中に1つの
inside the scribbles,
答えを見つけた
I found a single answer.
自分の価値に目を疑って
Doubting my own worth,
どこまでだって堕ちていけるの
just how far down can I fall?
どこか遠くに消えてしまいたい
I want to disappear somewhere far away.
こんな世界じゃ僕は要らない
In a world like this, I'm unneeded.
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun.
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
Raising your voice with a "Ready, set,"
聴こえてくるんだ
you can hear it coming.
自分の影の長さに気づく
Noticing the length of your own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already this late.
一等星が顔を出した
A first-magnitude star poked its face out.
届きそうで手を伸ばした
Reaching out a hand as if almost touching it,
次は僕についてきなよ
"Next, follow along with me,"
どんな暗闇でも
no matter how dark it is.
(もういいかい？ まだだよ)
"Ready yet?" "Not yet!"
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has begun to rise.
(もういいかい？ まだだよ)
"Ready yet?" "Not yet!"
色付けていくここから
Coloring it in, starting from right here.
10年後の僕らは
Ten years from now,
すれ違いばかりで
we'll just keep passing each other by.
幻想に想いを馳せては
Allowing my thoughts to roam in fantasies,
戻れない そう思い込んだ
I thought, "I can't go back."
くたびれた心に追いうちを
Pouring salt on a weary heart,
あの頃と変わらない夕日も
even the sunset, unchanged from back then,
なんとも思わない
doesn't make me feel anything at all.
自分を信じ歩いていければ
If only I could believe in myself and keep walking,
どこまでだって登れるのにな
I could climb anywhere, you know.
カットを跨ぐその空白に
In that blank space crossing the cut,
大切なもの見落としている
I'm overlooking something precious.
見つけられないと泣きわめく君へ
To you, crying and screaming because you can't find it...
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
raising your voice with a "Ready, set,"
聴こえてくるんだ
you can hear it coming.
自分の影の長さに気づく
Noticing the length of your own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already this late.
一等賞で駆け抜ける君
You, running ahead to take first prize...
くっついていただけの僕でも
even me, who was just clinging on behind,
君の前を歩けるかな？
can I walk ahead of you?
こんな頼りない僕でも
Even an unreliable person like me...
宝箱はホコリをかぶったまま
The treasure chest remains covered in dust.
無くした鍵はスッと
The lost key was quietly
君のポケットの中にあった
inside your pocket.
散らばっていた全てが
Everything that had been scattered
いまひとつに重なる
now overlaps into one.
手を取り始めよう
Let me take your hand and begin
僕たちの物語
our story.
一度はいらないと思った
Once, I thought I didn't need it.
いまなら胸を張れる気がしたんだ
Now I feel like I can hold my head high.
愛おしくて
So dear to me...
散らばっていた全てが
Everything that had been scattered,
愛おしくて
so dear to me,
いまひとつに重なる
now overlaps into one.
掛け声はいつも
The battle cry is always...
“いっせーのー”で声を上げて
raising your voice with a "Ready, set,"
聴こえてくるんだ
you can hear it coming.
自分の影の長さに気づく
Noticing the length of your own shadow,
もうこんな時間だ
it's already this late.
一等賞で駆け抜ける君
You, running ahead to take first prize...
くっついていただけの僕でも
even me, who was just clinging on behind,
君の前を歩けるかな？
can I walk ahead of you?
こんな頼りない僕でも
Even an unreliable person like me...
(もういいかい？ まだだよ)
"Ready yet?" "Not yet!"
泣きじゃくった声で
With a sobbing voice,
(もういいかい？ まだだよ)
"Ready yet?" "Not yet!"
笑う君が見えた
I saw you smiling.
(もういいかい？ まだだよ)
"Ready yet?" "Not yet!"
幕は上がりだした
The curtain has begun to rise.
(もういいかい？)
"Ready yet?"
もういいよ
"Ready now!"
色付けていくここから
Coloring it in, starting from right here.
曇天
[Title: Donten]
鉛の空 重く垂れ込み
The sky of lead hangs heavily down,
真白に淀んだ 太陽が砕けて
the pure white, stagnant sun breaks apart,
耳鳴りを 尖らせる
sharpening the ringing in my ears.
ひゅるり ひゅるり 低いツバメが
Whistling low, the swallows fly,
8の字なぞって ビルの谷を翔る
tracing figure eights, soaring through the valleys between buildings.
もうじきに 夕立が来る
Soon, an evening shower will fall.
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On this cloudy road, forgetting her umbrella,
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてる
she walks along, afraid of the rain.
ので僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
So I, hanging onto my cowardice as well,
空を仰ぐ
look up at the sky.
あちらこちら あんよは上手
Toddling along here and there,
珈琲屋に寄って 一休み決めたら
stopping by a coffee shop for a break,
帰れない 帰らない
I can't go back, I won't go back.
曇天の道を ぶらりぶらぶら
Wandering aimlessly down the cloudy road,
歩く二人は 足軽のごとく
the two of us walk like foot soldiers,
危険好きの誰かのふりをする
pretending to be daredevils who love danger,
小心者共
a pair of cowards.
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On this cloudy road, forgetting her umbrella,
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてる
she walks along, afraid of the rain.
ので僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
So I, hanging onto my cowardice as well,
空を仰ぐ
look up at the sky.
ほっといて育つもの
What is something that grows if you leave it alone?
なんだ なんだろ
What, I wonder what?
ワンモアチャンス ワンモアチャンス Never never give up!
One more chance, one more chance, never never give up!
ワンモアチャンス ワンモアチャンス Never give up!
One more chance, one more chance, never give up!
運営さん なんか放送エコーが切れてるかもしれないとのことで確認お願いします！
Staff-san, I heard the broadcast echo might be off, so please check on that!
出会いましては 簡単すぎるよ
Meeting someone is way too easy.
最初に決めた答えはひとつ
The answer I decided at first was just one.
ときめきました 合格しますか？
My heart fluttered! Did I pass?
恋も勝負も あわてない
I won't rush love or competition.
コツコツコツと 徹夜にため息
Working hard all night with a sigh.
私の中に 天才dreamer
Inside me is a genius dreamer.
思うことみな 叶えばいいな
I hope everything I dream comes true.
他人の世界は 気にしない
I won't worry about other people's worlds.
Perfect-area complete!
絶対ここで待ってるんだ
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area 望む声が聞こえるよ
Perfect-area, I can hear the voices hoping for it.
あー! イヤイヤ!!
Ah! Ear ear!!
Why? とまらないすれ違い
Why? Misunderstandings that never stop.
私があいさつ相手なら
If I were the one you asked for advice...
「友達かい？」「友達です。」 悲しき0点だね
"Are we friends?" "We're friends." That's a sad 0 out of 100!
No! やりなおしかきなおし 本気でワンモアチャンス
No! Redo it, rewrite it, seriously give me one more chance!
いまより素敵な未来があるのに
Even though there's a future more wonderful than now,
いまより素敵に my life, my life, my life!!
make my life even more wonderful than now, my life, my life!!
ありがとうございます！みんなありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you, everyone!
願いましましたよ 月にも星にも
I wished upon the moon and the stars.
科学的には どうにもならず
Scientifically, there was nothing to be done.
かがやき増した明日を 夢見て
Dreaming of a brighter tomorrow,
恋でガマンを学んだね
I learned patience through love.
ムクムクムクと広がる雨雲
Rain clouds spreading bigger and bigger,
私をぬらす瞬間スコール
a sudden squall soaking me in an instant.
悩みごとほら 流れたみたい
Look, all my worries seem to have washed away.
泣き言なんて忘れよう
Let me forget all about complaining.
Passive-nature conversation!
感動したいもっとずっと
I want to be moved much, much more.
Passive-nature 自分次第変われるよ
Passive-nature, I can change if I try!
はーい！いやーいやー！
Yay! No, no!
さり気なく聞いてみた
I nonchalantly asked around,
私の勉強不足で
due to my lack of studying,
可能性ありますか？
is there any possibility?
試験は何点かな？ Yeah!
What's my test score? Yeah!
誰だって 君だって
Anyone, even you,
間に合う ギリギリっしょ
can make it in time at the last minute!
これから始まる 季節にあいさつ
Greet the season that is about to begin.
これから始める My goal, My life, My light!
Starting right now: My goal, My life, My light!
気がついた ときには
By the time I noticed,
生まれてた なぜだろう
I was already born—I wonder why?
さあね
Who knows?
意識はもう 育ちつつあるよ
My consciousness is already growing,
強く 強くね
strongly, so strongly.
もう止まらない この気持ち
This feeling can't be stopped anymore!
私の勉強不足で
Due to my lack of studying,
可能性ありますか？
is there any possibility?
それとも0点かな？ No!
Or is it zero points? No!
やり直し 書き直し
Redo it, rewrite it,
本気でワンチャンっす！
for real, I've got a chance!
今より素敵な 未来があるから
Because there's a future more wonderful than now!
今より素敵に My goal, My life, My light!
Even more wonderfully than now: My goal, My life, My light!
はい！というわけで始まりましたー！
Alright! And so, it has begun!
2026年桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ！イエーイ！
Momosuzu Nene's Birthday Live 2026! Yay!
みんなコメントも見えてるよー ありがとうー！
I can see everyone's comments! Thank you!
エゴサ気づいてくれた人ありがとうー ねねこんな勢いで死んじゃうからw
Thanks to everyone who noticed my vanity searches! Nene's gonna die at this rate, lol!
はい！というわけで、今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
Okay! So, here's the hashtag for today!
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 です！
It's #MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026!
今ね、エゴサ機能がちょっとバグっちゃってるんで
Right now, the vanity search feature is glitching a bit,
こっちでツイートしてくれたらめっちゃ嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
so I'd be super happy if you tweet with this tag! Please do!
今日はね、超重大告知があるので
Today, I have a super important announcement,
最後まで楽しんでいってください！
so please enjoy until the very end!
さあ、今3曲お聞きいただいたんですけど
Now then, you've just heard three songs,
ねねの好きな曲... 銀魂、バカテスっていう感じでね
which are all songs Nene loves... like Gintama and BakaTest.
もうねねの好きな曲しかない3曲をやりましたけど
I performed three songs that are purely my absolute favorites,
3曲目に一番歌がきついの持ってきちゃって、ゼハゼハでございます！
but I put the most stamina-draining song 3rd, so I'm completely gasping for breath!
というわけで、ここからはゲストパートに入っていきます！
And so, from here on out, we're moving into the guest section!
それでは、VTRレッツゴー！
Now then, VTR, let's go!
抱きしめたいんだ！（パン パンパン）
I wanna hug you! (Clap, clap-clap)
かみしめたいんだ！（モンモン）
I wanna savor it! (Monmon)
おどかしたいんだ！
I wanna startle you!
今は我慢しよう coolish walk…
Let's hold back for now, coolish walk…
平常心が大事です。
Staying composed is important.
はゆる心を抑えて
Suppress your eager heart,
常識人になりましょう！
and let's act like sensible adults!
ヤバい人ならすぐなれる
Anyone can easily become a weirdo.
青い二人のヘヴン
The youthful heaven of the two of us.
子犬になる夢は（レア）
A dream of becoming a puppy (rare)
ユカイ特盛りの脳
in a brain heaped with fun.
トレースして（空を駆け回りたい）
Trace it (I want to run across the sky)
揺れる想いの下の果肉には
In the fruit flesh beneath swaying feelings,
恋の美味しさだけふくらんでる
only the sweetness of love is swelling up.
凄いメニューを作ると野望なら
If your ambition is to create an amazing menu,
まっとうにフルーツはぐくみましょう
let's nurture fruits properly.
高まりたいんだ！（パンパンパン）
I wanna get hyped! (Clap-clap-clap)
味わいたいんだ！（モンモン）
I wanna taste it! (Monmon)
オタケビたいんだ！
I wanna shout out loud!
そんな夢を見て coolish walk…
Dreaming such dreams, coolish walk…
対抗心はキケンです。
A competitive spirit is dangerous.
むかつく午後は深呼吸
Take a deep breath on an annoying afternoon,
優雅な大人きどりましょう
and let's pretend to be elegant adults!
キレル人は余ってる
Short-tempered people are everywhere.
甘い温度のソファー…
On a sofa of sweet warmth…
甘いミルクなささやきは 氷に
Sweet, milky whispers turning into ice,
流動するアイ
flow into love.
イメージして
Just picture it,
街を飛び跳ねよう
and let's leap through the town!
うるわしガール 天使のほっぺたに
On a lovely girl's angelic cheeks,
いっぱいなお願いが詰まってる
so many wishes are tightly packed inside.
誰も知らないストーリー 恐れないで
Don't be afraid of a story nobody knows.
まっすぐゴールを突き抜けましょう
Let's charge straight through to the goal!
遠いあこがれへ
Toward a distant longing,
時々見失うけど
even if we lose sight of it sometimes,
胸の涙のカケラ イレースしよう
let's erase the tear-drops in our hearts.
憂鬱 片付けよう
Let's clean away the gloom!
揺れる思いの下の果肉には
Beneath our swaying feelings lies a sweet fruit,
濃い美味しさだけ膨らんでる
bursting with rich flavor.
すごいメニューがやってくる と野望なら
If your ambition is a grand menu headed your way,
まっとうにフルーツ育みましょう
then let's properly nurture this fruit!
噛みしめたいんだ
I want to savor it!
躍動したいんだ
I want to leap into action!
今は我慢しよう
Let me hold back for now!
修行しよう
Let me train hard!
居合しよう
Let's hone our skills!
COOLISH WALK!
フレンズ
[Song: Friends]
口づけをかわした日は
On the day we shared a kiss,
ママの顔さえも見れなかった
I couldn't even look my mother in the eye.
ポケットのコインあつめて
Gathering the coins in our pockets,
ひとつずつ夢をかぞえたね
we counted our dreams one by one.
ほら あれは2人のかくれが
Look, over there was our secret hideout,
ひみつのメモリー oh
a secret memory... oh.
どこでこわれたの oh フレンズ
Where did it break... oh, friends?
うつむく日はみつめあって
On days we felt down, we looked at each other,
指をつないだら oh フレンズ
and when our fingers intertwined... oh, friends,
時がとまる気がした
I felt like time had stopped.
ねえ 君は覚えてる？
Hey, do you remember?
夕映えによく似合うあの曲
That song that suited the sunset so well.
だまりこむ君がいつも
Whenever you went silent,
悲しくてくちずさんだのに
you used to hum it so mournfully.
今 時は流れて セピアに染まるメロディー oh
Now, time has passed, leaving a sepia-toned melody... oh.
2度ともどれない oh フレンズ
We can never go back... oh, friends.
他人よりも遠くみえて
Seeming further apart than strangers,
いつも走ってた oh フレンズ
we were always running... oh, friends.
あの瞳がいとおしい
I miss those eyes of yours.
どこで 壊れたの Oh フレンズ
Where did it fall apart, oh friends?
うつむく日は 見つめ合って
On days when we cast our eyes down, looking at each other...
指をつないだら Oh フレンズ
When we held hands, oh friends,
時が止まる 気がした
I felt as if time had stopped.
ルーズな 踊れない Oh フレンズ
Loose and unable to dance, oh friends,
他人よりも 遠く見えて
You seemed further away than a stranger.
いつも 走ってた Oh フレンズ
Always running, oh friends,
あの瞳が 愛しい
Those eyes of yours are so precious to me.
Chu chu yeah!
Please me!
Without you!
あー！なんてことだ つたない過ちだ
Ah! What a mess, such a silly mistake!
自分のことに タララッタラッタ手焼く
Having such a hard time with myself.
どうして突然？ 逃げ切ったっていいでしょ？
Why all of a sudden? It's fine to just run away, right?
だけどなんだか気まぐれモードになり そんな気分になっちゃって
But somehow I got into a fickle mood, and felt just like doing so.
始まりはそんな風で
That's how it all started,
つまりはらしくないようで
which means it didn't really feel like me.
でも今じゃ扉開けてほら 声が聴こえるよ さあ
But now, open the door, look—I can hear voices calling out, come on!
行こう！
Let's go!
どこへでも
Anywhere we want!
僕らは君の翼になれる勇気があるよ
We have the courage to become your wings!
どんな試練も怖くない その魔法があるから
No trial is scary because we have that magic!
初めて出会う世界に 花束を贈ろう
Let's offer a bouquet of flowers to this world we meet for the first time!
ただこの瞬間 結ばれるよ
Just this moment, we are bound together.
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション？
Awkward communication?
でも別に構わない 明日から平和なら
But it doesn't matter, as long as tomorrow is peaceful!
Chu chu yeah!
Without you!
あー！どうしてまた素直になれなくて
Ah! Why can't I be honest with myself again?
自分のことで チュルルッチュルルッチュ火吹く
Breathing fire over my own problems!
ギアはそのまますぴーど上げていこう
Keep the gears in place and let me speed up!
だけどなんだか黄昏モードになり いつかを思い出させちゃって
But somehow I got into a twilight mood, remembering those old days.
一人でいても嫌じゃない
I don't mind being alone,
誰にも頼らなくてもいい
I don't have to rely on anyone.
でも扉の向こう騒がしい声が聴きたいよ 今
But I want to hear the noisy voices beyond the door right now!
行こう！
Let's go!
どこへでも
Anywhere we want!
僕らは君を背中に乗せて空を舞うよ
We'll carry you on our back and soar through the sky!
いつか心が離れても そのときは笑ってて
Even if our hearts drift apart someday, please be smiling then.
守りたいこの世界に 青空のラプソディ
In this world we want to protect, a rhapsody of the blue sky!
ただいつまでも奏でていてよ
Just keep playing it forever!
でこぼこなコンビネーション？
An uneven combination?
でも別に大丈夫さ 明日もまだ平和だ！
But it's totally fine, tomorrow will still be peaceful!
ほんの小さな傷を 太陽に晒して
Exposing our tiny wounds to the sun,
分け合ったよ、君と
I shared them with you,
痛みは暑さの中に溶けてく！
and the pain melts into the heat!
Chu chu yeah!
粋なビート弾く僕ら
Playing a stylish beat,
手をたたいて
Clap your hands!
ブギーなリズムで跳ねる二人
Bouncing to the boogie rhythm!
飛び跳ねてさ
Jumping up high!
いっせーのーで！
Ready, set, go!
イケてるビートで弾む僕ら
Bouncing along to a rockin' beat, we...
手を叩いて (Clap your hands!)
...clap our hands! (Clap your hands!)
ご機嫌なリズムで弾むアリーナ (みんな！)
The arena jumps to a cheerful rhythm! (Everyone!)
どこへ行っても
Wherever I go,
僕は君の翼になれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to become your wings.
灯火が無くても怖くない
Even without a light, I'm not afraid,
その魔法があるから
because I have that magic.
君と出会い世界は花束に溢れた
Meeting you, the world overflowed with bouquets.
ただその瞬間を繋げよう
Let's just connect those moments.
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション
Clumsy communication,
でも別に構わない
but it doesn't really matter,
明日が平和なら
as long as tomorrow is peaceful!
チュチュ イェイ！
Chu chu, yeah!
Please me!
一番賑やかな
The most lively...
理由を
...reason...
ちょうだい！
...give it to me!
はーい！
Yay!
やり切ったー！
We did it!
やり切りましたー！
We gave it our all!
ねね間違えたけど多分気付かれてないから大丈夫！
Nene messed up, but nobody noticed, so it's fine!
私も間違えました！
I messed up too!
あれ、みんな？大丈夫大丈夫！
Wait, all of us? It's fine, it's fine!
バレてない、バレてない！
Nobody noticed, nobody noticed!
えー、というわけで今日はねねの誕生日の記念ライブに可愛い後輩2人に来てもらいましたー！
So today, for Nene's birthday concert, two cute juniors came to join us!
ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
おめでとー！
Happy birthday!
キレのあるダンス！
Such sharp dancing!
変なキレを求められてる！
They were expecting weirdly sharp moves!
曲より動いてるから、今めっちゃ息切れしましたよ！
Moving more than the song required, I'm totally out of breath!
でも嬉しいですよ、呼んでいただいて！
But we're so happy you invited us!
来てくれると思ってなかったー！
I didn't think you'd actually come!
FLOW GLOWのライブ見てから、完成度が高すぎて一旦呼ぼうと思ったけど、やっぱやめようかなって...
After watching FLOW GLOW's live, it was so good that I thought about inviting you, then almost backed out...
なんでよ！なんでー！
Why?! Why?!
一緒にもできないと思ったけど...
I thought I wouldn't be able to keep up...
今回頑張っちゃいました！
...but I worked super hard this time!
嬉しかったー！
We were so happy!
デビューしてからの目標が、先輩と一緒にステージで歌って踊ることだったから...
Ever since our debut, our goal was to sing and dance on stage with our senpai...
それが今日叶ったー！
...and that came true today!
やったー！最高！
Yay! That's awesome!
えーじゃあ、最後に可愛くポーズ決めて写真撮って終わりにしようかなと思います！
Alright, let's finish off with a cute pose and take a picture!
可愛くですね！わかりました！
A cute pose, right? Got it!
全力でみんなそれぞれ可愛い感じでね！
Everyone give it your all with your own cute style!
フリじゃないよ？可愛くだよ！
It's not a joke setup, okay? Keep it cute!
いくよ、せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set...
いえーい！
Yay!
あれ？ちょっと待って！裏切ったな？！
Wait, hold on! Did you guys betray me?!
無口な ハート開いたら
When you open your quiet heart,
進もう 声合わせて
...let's move forward, joining our voices together!
キラキラ している自分を
The sparkling version of yourself...
掴もう
...let's seize it!
大好きな事しよう 勝ち負けだなんて 関係ないじゃない！
Let's do what we love! Winning or losing doesn't matter, right?!
さぁ手と手つないで Hey Jump! パーティは始まる Let's Dance 1,2,3!
Come on, hold hands and Hey Jump! The party is starting, Let's Dance 1,2,3!
未来へ そうずっと みんなで 絶対あきらめたくないから
To the future, that's right, always together, because we definitely don't want to give up!
Let's sing Do my best! 明日はきっと輝いてる
Let's sing Do my best! Tomorrow will surely be shining!
力合わせて トキメキ探していく つかみ取ろうプリパラ
Joining forces, we'll search for excitement, let's seize PriPara!
クヨクヨしている自分を
The self that is moping around...
変えよう みんながついてるよ
...let's change it! Everyone is right by your side!
ね？ 問題ないじゃない
See? It's no problem at all!
さあ 勇気を出して Hey!
Come on, muster up your courage, hey!
夢が始まる
Our dream is beginning!
3, 2, 1, GO!
Let's dance and sing! 未来へ
Let's dance and sing! Towards the future!
そう ずっと みんなで
Yes, always together with everyone,
絶対 手放したくないから
because I never want to let this go!
Let's keep my faith! 明日は
Let's keep my faith! Tomorrow
もっと 輝いてる
will shine even brighter!
希望を掲げて
Holding up our hopes high,
ドキドキ探してく
we'll search for heart-throbbing excitement.
誰のもの？ プリパラ
Who does it belong to? PriPara!
うまくいかないとか
When things aren't going well,
すれ違いばかりで
or when we keep passing by each other,
ダメになりそうな時は 一緒に
and it feels like we're about to give up, let's stay together.
二人折りの夢を叶えよう
Let's make our shared dream come true!
笑顔
Smile,
笑顔 受け取ろう
receive this smile!
そう 一緒に歌いたい
Yes, I want to sing together!
ね 一緒に踊りたい
Hey, I want to dance together!
絶対 諦めないよ
I definitely won't give up!
Let's go!
Let's dance and sing! 未来へ
Let's dance and sing! Towards the future!
そう ずっと みんなで
Yes, always together with everyone,
絶対 諦めたくないから
because I never want to give up!
Let's do my best! 明日は
Let's do my best! Tomorrow
きっと 輝いてる
will surely be shining!
力を合わせて トキメキ探してく
Joining our strength together, we'll search for heart-fluttering moments.
神アイドル プリパラ
Divine idols! PriPara!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ちょっと待って、一旦！
Wait a second, hold on!
ねねち、お誕生日おめでとう！
Nene-chi, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
コメントと30秒くらい差があるんだって。
Apparently there's about a 30-second delay with the comments.
一方的に声をかけることに…
We're just talking unilaterally then...
お邪魔してます！
Thanks for having us!
ていうか、ポルまろん！
By the way, Polmaron!
もうメン限にしよう！ メン限にしよう！
Let's make it member-only! Let me make it member-only!
ポルまろん、ちょっと喋れるようになったの？
Polmaron, can you talk a little bit now?
メン限でお知らせ…
I'll give an announcement in the member-only stream...
見てね！
Watch it, okay!
後でまた会いましょう！
Let's meet again later!
時間ない！ 時間ない！
No time! No time!
ポーズ撮って！ 行くよ！
Take a pose! Here we go!
面白いポーズで！
With a funny pose!
3, 2, 1...
無理無理無理無理無理！
Impossible, impossible, impossible!
正義なんです 私 恥じない
I'm righteous, I'm not ashamed!
なんてね
Just kidding!
トースト かじって
Nibbling on toast,
交差点で ぶつかる
bumping into each other at an intersection,
そういうんじゃないけど
it's not like that, but
予感は してたよ
I had a feeling.
きっとね 運命だね
Surely, it must be fate,
会えるって 信じてた
I believed we'd meet!
君専用の 笑顔 完璧だよ OK?
A smile made just for you, it's perfect, OK?
愚痴が出たり
Complaining sometimes,
ため息ついたり
or sighing out loud,
あるよね 分かるよ
that happens, right? I understand.
君が寂しくて 泣いてるなら
If you're lonely and crying,
イライラして たまらないなら
if you're so frustrated you can't stand it,
私の出番だな その手をとって 連れていくよ
it's my turn to step up! I'll take your hand and lead you away!
憂鬱なんて まばたきより 一瞬で
Gloominess will vanish in a blink, in an instant!
忘れちゃえ
Just forget about it!
とりあえずは 私だけ見ていて
For now, just look at me!
些細な隙間すら ちょっと考えられないくらい
So much that you can't think of even a tiny gap,
愛をあげる
I'll give you my love!
君が好きだ
I love you!
正義なんです 私 恥じない
I'm righteous, I'm not ashamed!
なんてね
Just kidding!
どうやら フラグは まだ立っていないみたいだ
It seems like the flag hasn't been raised yet.
そんなの気にしない 一直線に進むえ
I don't care about that, I'm charging straight ahead!
きっとね 定番ね お決まりのシチュエーション
I'm sure it's a classic, standard situation.
2人きりの空間 乾杯 OK
Just the two of us in this space, cheers, OK!
舞い上がっちゃって
Getting all excited,
後で反省会
only to hold a reflection session afterwards.
あるよね わかるよ
That happens, right? I totally get it.
脳内占拠して眠れないなら
If I take over your mind and you can't sleep,
ソワソワしてたまらないなら
if you're so restless you can't stand it,
いつだっておいでよ 少しずつ積み上げていこう
come over anytime, let's build this up step by step.
ようこそ 無限のパラダイム
Welcome to an infinite paradigm!
もういっそ ずっと一緒にいよう
Why not just stay together forever?
どこまでも 笑っていてね
Keep smiling no matter where we go.
もっと視線ほしいんだ
I want you to look at me more.
そっと掴んだシャツの裾
Gently tugging the hem of your shirt,
最上級をプレゼントしよう
I'll give you the absolute best present!
難しく考えなくてもいいよ
You don't need to overthink it.
ただただ 楽しいを続けよう
Let's just keep having fun!
繋いだ今日が 明日になっていくんだ
The today we connected will become tomorrow.
よーそろー 全速前進で とんでもない景色見に行こう
Full speed ahead! Let's go see incredible sights!
乗りかかった船でしょう
We're already in the same boat, after all!
そこそこの装備じゃ もう満足できないくらい
So much that basic equipment won't satisfy you anymore,
夢中になれる 夢中にさせる
I can get absorbed in it, and make you absorbed too!
ようこそ 無敵のテーマパーク
Welcome to an invincible theme park!
もういっそ 全部忘れちゃえ
Just forget about everything else!
とりあえすは 私だけ見て
For now, just look at me.
底なしの沼だぞ
It's a bottomless pit, you know!
ちょっと考えられないくらい
Almost beyond imagination,
愛をあげる 君が好きだ
I'll give you my love, I like you!
時間なんて関係ないファン
Time doesn't matter to fans,
今だって ほら笑って
look, even now, give us a smile!
じゃんけん提案です 私負けない
How about a game of rock-paper-scissors? I won't lose!
なんてね
Just kidding!
突然降る夕立 あぁ傘もないや嫌
A sudden evening shower—ah, I don't even have an umbrella, I hate this!
空のご機嫌なんか知らん
I don't care about the sky's mood.
季節の変わり目の服は何着りゃいいんだろ
What clothes should I wear during the change of seasons?
春と秋どこ行っちゃったんだよ
Where did spring and autumn even go?
息も出来ない 情報の圧力
Can't even breathe under the pressure of information.
めまいの螺旋だ わたしはどこにいる
A dizzying spiral—where am I?
こんなに こんなに 息の音がするのに
Even though my breathing sounds so loud, so loud,
変だね 世界の音がしない
It's strange—I can't hear the world's sound.
足りない 足りない 誰にも気づかれない
Not enough, not enough—no one notices me.
殴り書きみたいな音出せない状態で叫んだよ
Unable to make a rough, scribbled sound, I screamed out!
「ありのまま」なんて誰に見せるんだ
Show "my true self"? To whom?
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
Foolish as I am, I just sing.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Shall I just spill it all out to the stars?
エリクサーに張り替える作業もなんと無くなんだ
Changing to Elixir strings somehow feels pointless.
欠けた爪を少し触る
I gently touch my chipped fingernail.
半径300mmの体で必死に鳴いてる
With a body of 300mm radius, crying out desperately,
音楽にとっちゃ ココが地球だな
To music, this right here is Earth.
空気を握って 空を殴るよ
Gripping the air, I punch the sky!
なんにも起きない わたしは無力さ
Nothing happens—I am powerless.
だけどさ その手で この鉄を弾いたら
But still, when I pluck these iron strings with that hand,
何かが変わって見えた…ような。
it felt like... something had changed.
眩しい 眩しい そんなに光るなよ
Dazzling, so dazzling—don't shine so bright!
わたしのダサい影が
My uncool shadow
より色濃くなってしまうだろ
Will become darker
なんでこんな熱くなっちゃってんだ 止まんない
Yet, why am I getting so fired up? It won't stop
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
So I'm singing just like the fool I am
うるさいんだって 心臓
My heart won't shut up
蒼い惑星 ひとりぼっち
All alone on this blue planet
いっぱいの音を聞いてきた
I've heard lots of sounds
回り続けて 幾億年
Continuously rotating for billions of years
一瞬でもいいから... ああ
Even if it's just for a moment... ah
聞いて 聴けよ
Listen, listen to me!
わたし わたし わたしはここにいる
I am, I am, I am right here
殴り書きみたいな音出せない状態で叫んだよ
When I couldn't even make a sound, I tried to scream louder
なんかになりたい なりたい 何者かでいい
I want to be something, anything is fine
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
So I'm singing just like the fool I am
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Entrusting my thoughts to the stars
イエーイ！
Yay!
ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！ / ありがとう！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday! / Thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
イエーイ！
Yay!
というわけで、ReGLOSSから奏ちゃんに来てもらいました！
So, we have Kanade-chan from ReGLOSS with us today!
イエーイ！音乃瀬奏です！お邪魔しまーす！
Yay! I'm Otonose Kanade! Thanks for having me!
今回はね、ねね、普段の奏ちゃんとの喋りと歌のギャップが大好きで
Nene loves the gap between Kanade-chan's usual talking and her singing!
普段これじゃん！
She's normally like this!
普段これだけど、歌うと急にね、なんか切ない、エモい感じで...
She's normally like this, but when she sings, she suddenly gets all emotional...
えー！嬉しい！
Aw, I'm so happy!
ねね先輩に言ってもらえるととっても嬉しい！
Hearing that from you makes me so happy, Nene-senpai!
そのイメージがめっちゃ好きで、一緒にそういうギャップが出る曲を歌いたいなと思って
I really love that image, so I wanted to sing a song together that highlights that gap.
お誘いしてみました！受けてくれてありがとう！
So I invited her! Thanks for accepting!
ねね先輩もめっちゃかっこよかったですよ！
You were super cool too, Nene-senpai!
あと、髪の毛のさ、色もさ...
Also, our hair color...
確かに！同じ金髪からピンクのグラデーション！
That's true! We both have yellow-to-pink gradient hair!
そんな親近感もあるかなと思ってお誘いしてみました。
I felt a sense of familiarity, so I decided to invite her.
こちらこそありがとうございます！一緒に歌えてとっても嬉しかったです！
Thank you as well! I was so happy to sing together!
奏ちゃんのね、ダンスの覚え方が可愛いんだよ。
The way Kanade-chan memorizes dances is so cute.
え？そうですか？
Huh? Really?
「忍者、忍者...」って
Like "Ninja, ninja..."
覚え方が「こうなってて、忍者、忍者...」って
The way she memorized it was "It goes like this, ninja, ninja..."
先生もめっちゃ笑顔だったよ！
Even the teacher was smiling!
えーっと、じゃあ...
Um, well then...
最後にちょっとギャップのある感じで、スクショ...
Finally, let me take a screenshot with that gap vibe...
任せてください！ / 「任せてください」なの？
Leave it to me! / "Leave it to me"?
ねねもちょっとかっこいい、エモい感じで、孤独な感じで...
I'll try to look cool, emotional, and lonely too...
任せてください！いきますよ！ / いこう！
Leave it to me! Here we go! / Let's go!
音...！ / 今なにやったの？
Sound...! / What was that just now?
ちょっとかっこいいエモい感じで...
Trying to look cool and emotional...
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms bloom
見慣れたいつもの坂道に
On the familiar hill road as always
ああ 別れを
Ah, saying goodbye
泣いて笑ったあの日々
Those days of tears and laughter
なんだか昨日のことのよう
Feel like they were just yesterday
この道はそう
This path, yes,
未来へ
to the future...
続く道
is the path that continues forward,
そんな気がしたの
I felt that way.
例年より早い
Earlier than usual,
開花予想を
the cherry blossom forecast
キミは嬉しがってた
made you so happy.
私は笑って
I smiled and said,
「そうだね」って言った
"I guess so."
あと少ししたらもう
In just a little while longer,
ここには戻れないのに
we won't be able to return here anymore, and yet...
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
These feelings I can't express well in words,
キミに打ち明けるとしたらなんて
if I were to open up and tell you,
伝えよう 最初で最後
how should I say it? For the first and last time...
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The path we walked home together back then
私にとって特別な思い出
is a special memory for me.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget—goodbye memories.
春が来たら
When spring arrives,
それぞれの道を
we will take our separate paths.
また会える日を
Praying for the day
願って
we can meet again,
さよなら
"Goodbye,"
小さくつぶやいた
I softly whispered.
空はあの頃と
The sky is just as blue
変わらず青くて
as it was back then,
だからちょっと泣けた
and that's why I cried a little.
わざと遠回りしたの
I intentionally took a detour,
少しでも長くキミの隣にいたくて
wanting to stay by your side for as long as possible.
私はおどけて
I played it off foolishly
「まちがえた!」って言った
and said, "I made a wrong turn!"
キミは笑う その顔が
You laughed, and your face
まぶしくて目をそらした
was so dazzling that I looked away.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
Holding feelings in my heart that words cannot express,
胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
I walked along this path.
覚えてる あの時キミは
I remember... back then, you
私の名前を呼んでくれた
called out my name
二人 夕暮れの帰り道で
as the two of us walked home in the sunset.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget—goodbye memories.
出会えた事
I'm so grateful
感謝してる
that I met you.
初めて見た
The cherry blossoms in full bloom
満開の桜
that we saw together for the first time...
あれからどれくらい
How much have I changed
変われたんだろう
since that day?
一目見た時に思ったんだ
The moment I first saw you, I thought,
この人の事好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall in love with this person."
なんでかな? わかんないよ
I wonder why? I don't even know.
それからの毎日 はとても楽しくて
Every day after that was so much fun,
だけど同じくらいに辛かったんだ
but it was just as painful too.
あぁ ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
Ah, I'm sorry... I can't put it well into words.
だから私 キミと なんていうか
That's why I, with you... how should I say this?
今のまま
Leaving things as they are right now...
さよならしたくないよ
I don't want to say goodbye.
友達のままじゃ
Remaining just friends...
もう嫌なの
I don't want that anymore.
言おうと思ってた 私 キミの
What I wanted to tell you was... I...
キミのことずっと
I've loved you all this time,
ずっと前から
since way back then,
好きでした
I've always loved you.
あぁ やっと言えた
Ah... I was finally able to say it.
いつだって君は笑われものだ
You're always someone who gets laughed at,
やることなすことついてなくて
and nothing you do ever goes right.
あげくに雨に降られ
On top of that, you get caught in the rain,
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
and your favorite umbrella gets blown away by the wind.
そこのノラはご苦労様と
A stray cat nearby steps on your foot,
足を踏んづけてった
as if saying, "Better luck next time."
いつも通り君は嫌われものだ
As usual, you're someone who is disliked,
なんにもせずとも遠ざけられて
shunned without even doing anything.
努力もしてみるけど
You try your best anyway,
その理由なんて「なんとなく？」で
but when asked why, they just say "No real reason."
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
You were completely at a loss, feeling so sad.
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
If that's the case, you can use my voice.
人によっては理解不能で
To some, it's completely incomprehensible,
なんて耳障り ひどい声だって
and they might say it's harsh and terrible,
言われるけど
but still,
きっと君の力になれる
I know it can surely help you.
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So go ahead and let me sing.
そう君の
That's right, with your...
君だけの言葉で
...with your words alone.
綴って
Compose them,
連ねて
string them together,
あたしがその思想を叫ぶから
'cause I'll shout those thoughts out loud.
描いて
Paint them,
理想を
your ideals,
その思いは誰にも触れさせない
and I won't let anyone touch those feelings.
ガラクタの声はそして響く
And so, the voice of trash resounds,
ありのままを不器用に繋いで
clumsily connecting things just as they are,
精一杯に大声を上げる
shouting at the top of its lungs.
いつからか君は人気者だ
Before long, you became popular,
たくさんの人に持てはやされ
praised and fawned over by so many,
あたしも鼻が高い
and I felt proud too.
でもいつからか君は変わった
But somewhere along the way, you changed,
冷たくなって だけど寂しそうだった
becoming cold, yet looking so lonely.
「もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
"I've had enough of a machine's voice.
僕は僕自身なんだよ」って
I am my own person," you said,
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
unable to hold it in any longer,
あたしを嫌った
until you grew to hate me.
君の後ろで誰かが言った
Behind your back, someone said,
虎の威を借りる狐のくせに！
"You're just borrowed power!"
ねえ 君は一人で泣いてたんだね
Hey, you were crying all alone, weren't you?
聴こえる？この声
Can you hear it? This voice...
あたしがその誹謗をかき消すから
...I'll drown out all that slander for you.
分かってる
I know,
本当は
the truth is,
君が誰より優しいってことを
you're kinder than anyone else.
ガラクタの声はそして歌った
And so, the voice of trash sang,
他の誰でもない君のために
for you and no one else,
きしんでいく 限界を超えて
creaking along, pushing beyond its limits.
二人はどんなにたくさんの言葉を
How many words must the two of us...
思いついたことだろう
...have thought up together?
だけど今は何ひとつ思いつかなくて
Yet now, not a single word comes to mind,
だけど何もかも分かった
but everything finally makes sense.
「そうか、きっとこれは夢だ。
"I see, this must be a dream.
永遠に覚めない、
A dream where I met you,
君と会えた、そんな夢」
that I will never wake up from."
ガラクタは幸せそうな顔をしたまま
With a happy look on its face, the trash...
どれだけ呼んでももう動かないの
...no longer moves, no matter how much you call out.
望んだはずの結末に君は泣き叫ぶ
At the ending you thought you wanted, you cry out,
「嘘だろ 嘘だろ」ってそう泣き叫ぶ
screaming, "It's a lie, tell me it's a lie!"
「僕は無力だ
"I'm so powerless,
ガラクタひとつだって救えやしない」
I can't even save a single piece of trash!"
思いは...
My feelings...
想いは 涙に
My feelings turn to tears,
ぽつり ぽつりと
bit by bit,
その頬を濡らす
wetting those cheeks.
そのとき
At that moment,
世界は とたんに
the world instantly
その色を
changes its color
大きく変える
in a big way.
ああ 悲しみ
Ah, sadness,
喜び
joy,
すべてを ひとりと
everything, alone and as one,
ひとつは知った
became understood.
言葉は歌になり
My words turn into songs,
この世界を
and once again
再び駆け巡る
travel across this world
君のために
for your sake.
その声に
Entrusting intentions
意思を宿して
into that voice,
今 想いが響く
now, those feelings resound.
はい！ ポルカがハモリじゃないよ、みんな！ ねねの声だよ～！
Yes! That wasn't Polka doing harmony, everyone! That was Nene's voice~!
というわけで、ゲストにいっぱい来ていただきまして、いっぱい色んな歌歌えて楽しかったです！
So, we had so many guests join us, and I had a lot of fun singing all kinds of songs!
ちなみに『フレンズ』はママのチョイスです！ みんな「ママのチョイスかな？」って言ってたから大正解です！
By the way, "FRIENDS" was Mom's choice! Everyone was asking, "Is it Mom's choice?" so you were totally right!
じゃあ、告知行きたいと思います！ まずはこちら！
Now then, let's move on to the announcements! First, this!
桃鈴ねね 誕生記念2026グッズが発売されます！ まずはこちら！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2026 merch is going on sale! First, this!
ワイドラバーマット！ 上目遣いでねねが上を見ながら、みんなに「お願い」ってしてるイラストで...
Wide Rubber Mat! An illustration of Nene looking up with upturned eyes like she's pleading with everyone...
イラストはまもる先生描き下ろしで、横幅がめっちゃ広いので、キーボードやマウスを置いてデスクで使ってください！
The illustration is specially drawn by Mamoru-sensei. It's super wide, so please put your keyboard and mouse on it and use it at your desk!
さっきの同じキービジュアルを使った前面はTシャツ、後面は「尊き桃鈴」って書いてあるTシャツです！
Using the same key visual, this T-shirt has the illustration on the front, and "Precious Momosuzu" written on the back!
前に出した「やっぱり桃鈴」に続く「尊き桃鈴」のTシャツができました！ ぜひ着てください！ 「尊いか」「やっぱりか」選んでね！
Following the "As Expected of Momosuzu" shirt from before, the "Precious Momosuzu" T-shirt is complete! Please wear it! Choose between "Precious" or "As Expected"!
ランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！ 色んな衣装のねねが可愛いポーズをしています！ イラストは花柱ゆのき先生に描いてもらいました！
Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keychains! Nene in various outfits striking cute poses! The illustrations were drawn by Hananashi Yunoki-sensei!
台座とボールチェーンが付いているので、ミニアクスタとしても使えるし、キーホルダーとしても使えます！ そして次、こちら！
It comes with a base and a ball chain, so you can use it as a mini acrylic stand or a keychain! And next, this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー 私服衣装ver.！ これめっちゃこだわって作ってて、可愛さ全振りのねねの私服衣装ぬいぐるみキーホルダーになります！ ボールチェーン付きなのでカバンにつけて一緒にお出かけしてね！
Plushie Keychain (Casual Outfit ver.)! We put so much care into this, focusing 100% on cuteness for Nene's casual outfit plushie keychain! It has a ball chain, so attach it to your bag and go out together!
前髪とか顔とか凄いこだわって作ったので絶対可愛い自信あります！ 実物今度見せたいと思います！ そしてラスト！ ボイスです！
We were super meticulous with the bangs and face, so I'm totally confident in its cuteness! I'll show you the real thing next time! And lastly, the voice pack!
シチュエーションボイス「ねねときみのお誕生日」！ ねねがみんなのお誕生日も祝ってあげたいと思います、しょうがないので！ 今すぐ聴いてもいいし、自分の誕生日に聴いてもよし！
Situation Voice "Nene and Your Birthday"! Nene wants to celebrate everyone's birthday too, since I have to! You can listen right away, or listen on your own birthday!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！ 数量限定版は直筆サインと複製箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード！ 通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージが入っています！ 数量限定版今回もありますのでよろしくお願いします！
And here are the full set purchase bonus items! The limited quantity version includes a postcard with a handwritten signature and duplicated foil-stamped message! The regular version has a foil-stamped duplicated signature and message!
さらにボイスもついてきます！ 「毎日一番に見てほしいの！」ってことで、幼馴染のねねが朝からのっかかってくるシチュエーションボイスです！
Plus, a bonus voice pack is included! Titled "I Want You to Look at Me First Every Day!", featuring Nene as your childhood friend jumping on you in the morning!
特典もたくさんあるので、ぜひフルセットで買ってください！ この後 21:30 から販売開始です！ よろしくお願いします！ そして...
There are lots of bonus items, so please buy the full set! Sales start after this at 21:30! Thank you! And...
オリ曲のMVが出ます！ Liminal！ 本日MVは 21:15 からを予定しています！ リリースは 3月3日 の 0:00 から！
The MV for my original song is coming out! Liminal! Today's MV release is scheduled for 21:15! Stream release starts on March 3rd at 0:00!
よろしくお願いします！ どんな曲だろうね！ 今回のライブのタイトルにもなってます！ そして！ 超重大告知があります！ こちら！
Thank you! I wonder what kind of song it is! It's also the title of today's live concert! And! I have a super important announcement! This!
『Peachful Story』！ 桃鈴ねねの 1st アルバムが... この後 21時... あ、今！ ちょうど今 21時から始まりましたー！ イェーイ！ 初回生産限定盤と通常盤の2種類あります！
"Peachful Story"! Momosuzu Nene's 1st album... starts at 21:00... Ah, right now! Just now at 21:00, sales started~! Yay! There are two versions: First Press Limited Edition and Regular Edition!
通常盤はこちら！ りいちゅ先生が描いてくれた通常盤のやつと... ランダムのアナザージャケットがついてきます！ なんと！ こちら！ ドン！
The Regular Edition is this! The regular edition drawn by Riichu-sensei... and it comes with a random alternative jacket! What's more, look at this! Ta-da!
イナちゃんとラオーラちゃんに描いてもらいましたー！ マイク持ってる方がイナちゃんで、踊ってる方がラオーラちゃんが描いてくれました！ ありがとうー！ 数量限定で直筆サインが入っているので、みんなぜひチェックしてください！
Ina-chan and Raora-chan drew them for me~! The one holding the mic was drawn by Ina-chan, and the one dancing was drawn by Raora-chan! Thank you~! These have handwritten signatures in limited quantities, so please check them out!
リバーシブル仕様の直筆サイン入りアナザージャケット
Reversible alternate cover with a handwritten signature!
どっちをね、表にして主役にしてもいいですし
You can make either side the main cover on front,
なんなら2個買っていただいて両方とも表面にして、ねねとねねをがっちゃんこさせてください！
or buy two and display both sides so Nene and Nene are side-by-side!
そして、えーこちらがついてきます。
And this comes with it too.
えーレコーディングブックと、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの、えーカードがついてきます！
It comes with a recording book and a Hololive Official Card Game card!
ねねのね、どんな感じで歌ってたーとか、ここ怒られたーとかそういうのがまとまったノートになってまーす！
It's a notebook packed with details like how I sang and where I got scolded!
そして！もう一つあります！なんと！
And there's one more thing! Believe it or not!
こちら！
This!
「ねねねのね！」ねねの1st EP、グッズとして出させたね、ねねのCDが復刻になりますー！イェーイ！
"Nenenenone!", my 1st EP that was released as merch, is getting a reprint! Yay!
これね、あの、意外と多分持ってる人少ないんじゃないかなーと思います。
I think surprisingly few people own this one.
あの、今までのねねのね、あの有名な曲たちが掲載されていますので、こちらの復刻版もぜひ聴いて、今回のアルバムと一緒に全曲聴いて覚えてほしいなーって思います！
It includes my famous songs so far, so please check out this reprint and learn all the songs together with the album!
さて、さっきLiminalのMVの告知をしたと思うんですけど、どんな曲か聴きたいよね、みんな？
Now, I announced the MV for Liminal earlier, but I bet everyone wants to hear what kind of song it is!
それじゃあ、ねね、今からしっとりとやっていこうかなと思います。
So now, Nene is going to sing it with a quiet, emotional feel.
それでは聴いてください。「Liminal」。
Please listen. "Liminal".
見つめる くすんだ瞳で
Staring with dull eyes,
光を探して迷ってた
I was lost, searching for the light.
いくつもの痛みに 縛られたまま 頬を伝う
Bound by so many pains, tears run down my cheeks.
画面に映る私はどうして 涙の跡が消されているんだろう
Why are the traces of tears erased from my reflection on screen?
罅割れた硝子の向こう 笑って繕っていた 誰かがいた
Behind the cracked glass, someone was putting on a fake smile.
「偽物みたいだ」
"It feels like a fake,"
「ただの影だ」って
"Just a shadow,"
決め付けたけど
I had assumed, but...
まやかしじゃなくて 私が私でいる理由を
It wasn't an illusion; the reason I am myself,
君の笑顔に 貰っていた
I received from your smile.
そうさ 画面の中
Yes, inside the screen,
隠せない 消えない 見えない
I can't hide, I can't fade, I can't be seen,
それでも それでも 私 は
Even so, even so, I...
君の光を追って
chase after your light,
閉じこもる暗い硝子の 曇りを払って
clearing the fog from the dark glass I hide behind.
今 明日を見つけたんだ
Now, I have found tomorrow.
忘れたくない 君がくれた この感情を
I never want to forget this emotion you gave me.
見つめる 姿鏡の奥の
Looking into the depths of the full-length mirror,
涙の跡は見せられないけど
I cannot show the traces of my tears, but...
磨かれた硝子の向こう 笑って輝いていた
Behind the polished glass, someone was smiling and shining,
いたかっただけで
I just wanted to be there.
「誰のためだっけ？」
"Who was it for again?"
声が 姿が 誰でもない気がした
My voice and my appearance felt like nobody at all.
「孤独だ」って また迷い出す
Saying "I'm all alone," I get lost once more.
画面の奥の歪みを いつでも
The distortion behind the screen, always,
いつでも 君は
always, you...
映す光の中に 名もない私の声を 見つけてくれてた
In the reflecting light, you were finding my nameless voice.
ずっと
Always...
「この声も、姿も、紛れもない私だ」
"This voice, this form, are unmistakably me."
「ありのままでいいんだ」
"It's okay to just be myself."
「この気持ちは本物だ」
"These feelings are real."
縛られても
Even if I am bound,
触れられなくても
Even if I can't touch you,
君が示してくれてたから
Because you showed me the way...
いつかこの「私」で
Someday, as this "me,"
ずっと光を手繰って
Continuously pulling the light closer...
きっと見つけ出す
I will surely find you...
誰でもない「君」に会えるまで
Until I meet the "you" like no other.
境界線はすぐそこに
The boundary line is right there.
そうさ 画面の向こう
Yes, beyond the screen...
それこそ それこそ 私なんだ
That is precisely who I am!
君と光になって
Becoming light together with you,
未だ遮る硝子の壁の先まで
To beyond the glass wall that still blocks us,
届くように笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling so I can reach you.
迷いはない
There is no hesitation.
君がくれたこの感情と
With these feelings you gave me...